A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991, RG 39 FA1505
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991; 39
  - Medicine, 1987-1991; 17
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Executive Committee (Box 383, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Institutional Policy Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 383, Folder 2-3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Institutional Policy Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 383, Folder 4-6)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Institutional Policy Committee and Long-Range Planning Subcommittee, 1988 (Box 384, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Long-Range Planning Subcommittee of the Institutional Policy Committee, 1987 (Box 384, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Joint Organizational Policy Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 384, Folder 3-5)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Presidents Council (Box 385, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Printed Matter (Box 385, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Rockefeller Research Laboratories (Box 385, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Rockefeller Research Laboratories - A-Z (Box 385, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Rockefeller Research Laboratories - Dedication (Box 386, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Rockefeller Research Laboratories - Laurance S. Rockefeller Board Room (Box 386, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Rockefeller Research Laboratories - Laurance S. Rockefeller Board Room - Fundraising (Box 386, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Memorial Hospital for Cancer and Allied Diseases (Box 387, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - S.K.I. Realty (Box 387, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Sloan-Kettering Institute (Box 387, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (Box 387, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - A-Z (Box 387, Folder 5)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Contributions (Box 387, Folder 6)
    - Hospitals - Montefiore Medical Center (Box 388, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Phelps Memorial Hospital Center (Box 388, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Phelps Memorial Hospital - Cousins (Box 373, Folder 14)
      Restricted - Living Rockefeller family members
    - Hospitals - St. John's Hospital, Jackson, Wyoming (Box 388, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Society of New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center (Box 388, Folder 4, Box 389, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Society of New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Contributions (Box 389, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Society of New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Printed Matter (Box 389, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - United Hospital Fund of New York (Box 390, Folder 1)
    - Mental Health - A-Z (Box 390, Folder 2-5)
    - Mental Health - A-Z - Cousins (Box 373, Folder 15-16)
    - Mental Health - C.G. Jung Institute of Los Angeles (Box 390, Folder 6, Box 391, Folder 1)
    - Mental Health - C.G. Jung institute of San Francisco (Box 391, Folder 2-3)
    - Mental Health - The Lifwynn Foundation (Box 391, Folder 4)
    - Mental Health - Recoveries Anonymous (Box 391, Folder 5)
    - Narcotics - A-Z (Box 392, Folder 1)
    - Narcotics - A-Z - Cousins (Box 373, Folder 17)
    - Narcotics - Phoenix House (Box 392, Folder 2)
    - Narcotics - Phoenix House - Cousins (Box 373, Folder 18)
  - N-P, 1987-1991; 18
    - N - Miscellaneous (Box 392, Folder 3)
    - O - Miscellaneous (Box 392, Folder 4)
    - P - Miscellaneous (Box 392, Folder 5)
  - Philanthropy, 1987-1991; 19
    - Philanthropy - A-M (Box 392, Folder 6)
    - Philanthropy - N-Z (Box 393, Folder 1)
    - Philanthropy - A-Z - Cousins (Box 373, Folder 19-20)
    - Clippings (Box 393, Folder 2)
    - Council on Foundations (Box 393, Folder 3)
    - Family Philanthropy Committee (Box 396, Folder 1)
    - Howe, Fisher (Box 393, Folder 4)
    - Independent Sector (Box 393, Folder 5)
    - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy (Box 396, Folder 2)
    - Philanthropy Quarterly (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - Politics, 1987-1991; 20
    - Politics - A-O (Box 394, Folder 2-6)
    - Politics - P-Z (Box 395, Folder 1-2)
    - Politics - A-Z - Cousins (Box 396, Folder 3-7)
    - Coalition for a New Foreign Policy (Box 396, Folder 8)
    - Cohen, William S. (Box 395, Folder 3)
    - Common Cause (Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Democracy Project (Box 397, Folder 2)
    - Fund for Constitutional Government (Box 397, Folder 3-4, Box 398, Folder 1)
    - The Future Fund (Box 398, Folder 2-3)
    - Human Serve Fund (Box 395, Folder 4)
    - Institute for Public Policy Advocacy (Box 399, Folder 1-2)
    - Joint Center for Political Studies, Inc. (Box 395, Folder 5)
    - League of Rural Voters Education Project (Box 399, Folder 3, Box 400, Folder 1)
    - Maine Nuclear Referendum Committee (Box 400, Folder 2)
    - National Republican Congressional Committee (Box 403, Folder 1)
    - New York Republican County Committee (Box 403, Folder 2)
    - New York Republican State Committee (Box 403, Folder 3)
    - The Public Agenda Foundation (Box 403, Folder 4)
    - The Public Agenda Foundation - Cousins (Box 400, Folder 3, Box 401, Folder 1-2)
    - Public Citizen (Box 401, Folder 3, Box 402, Folder 1-3)
    - Republican National Committee and Republican National Finance Committee (Box 403, Folder 5)
    - Republican National Senatorial Committee (Box 404, Folder 1)
    - Republican Senate House Dinner (Box 404, Folder 2)
    - Ripon Society (Box 404, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, John D. IV (Box 404, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, John D. IV - Cousins (Box 409, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, John D. IV - Clippings (Box 404, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Public Interest Research Group (Box 409, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Contributions - A-J (Box 405, Folder 1-5)
    - Miscellaneous Contributions - K-R (Box 406, Folder 1-3)
    - Miscellaneous Contributions - S-Z (Box 407, Folder 1-2)
    - Miscellaneous Contributions - A-E - Cousins (Box 409, Folder 3-5)
    - Miscellaneous Contributions - F-P - Cousins (Box 410, Folder 1-4)
    - Miscellaneous Contributions - Q-Z - Cousins (Box 411, Folder 1-3)
  - Population, 1987-1991; 21
    - Population - A-Z (Box 407, Folder 3-4)
    - Population - A-Z - Cousins (Box 411, Folder 4-5)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America, Inc. (Box 408, Folder 1)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America, Inc. - Cousins (Box 411, Folder 6)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America, Inc. - New York City (Box 408, Folder 2)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America, Inc. - New York City - Cousins (Box 411, Folder 7)
    - Population Council (Box 408, Folder 3)
    - Population Council - Contributions (Box 408, Folder 4)
    - Population Council - Finances (Box 408, Folder 5)
    - Population Council - Fundraising (Box 408, Folder 6)
    - Population Council - Meetings, 1987-1989 (Box 412, Folder 1-3)
    - Population Crisis Committee (Box 413, Folder 1)
    - Population Crisis Committee - Cousins (Box 411, Folder 8)
    - Abortion - A-Z (Box 413, Folder 2)
    - Abortion - A-Z - Cousins (Box 411, Folder 9)
    - Abortion - National Abortion Rights Action League (NARAL) Foundation (Box 413, Folder 3, Box 414, Folder 1)
    - Abortion - National Abortion Rights League (NARAL) Foundation - Cousins (Box 411, Folder 10)
  - Q-R, 1987-1991; 22
    - Q - Miscellaneous (Box 414, Folder 2)
    - R - Miscellaneous (Box 414, Folder 3)
  - Race Relations, 1987-1991; 23
    - Race Relations - A-Z (Box 414, Folder 4)
    - Race Relations - A-Z - Cousins (Box 411, Folder 11)
    - The Catholic Interracial Council of New York (Box 414, Folder 5)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) (Box 414, Folder 6)
    - National Association for Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) - Cousins (Box 411, Folder 12)
    - National Urban League (Box 414, Folder 7)
    - New York Urban Coalition (Box 415, Folder 1)
    - New York Urban Coalition - Cousins (Box 411, Folder 13)
    - New York Urban League (Box 415, Folder 2)
    - New York Urban League - Cousins (Box 411, Folder 14)
    - Southern Regional Council (Box 415, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate, 1987-1991; 24
    - Real Estate - A-Q (Box 415, Folder 4-6)
    - Real Estate - R-Z (Box 416, Folder 1)
    - Algernon Blair Group, Inc. (Box 416, Folder 2)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel (Box 416, Folder 3)
    - Embarcadero Center and Embarcadero Center West (Box 416, Folder 4)
    - Enterprise Foundation (Box 416, Folder 5, Box 417, Folder 1)
    - Estate Fountain River - Patrick J. Wells (Box 418, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Open in 2042.
    - R.D. Evans Development Corporation (Box 417, Folder 2)
    - Greenrock - Pocantio Hills - A-Z (Box 418, Folder 2-3)
    - Greenrock - Pocantio Hills - Employees (Box 418, Folder 4)
    - Greenrock - Pocantio Hills - Finances (Box 418, Folder 5, Box 419, Folder 1-2)
    - Greenrock - Pocantico Hills - 5600-Joint Office Billing (Box 420, Folder 1)
    - Greenrock - Pocantico Hills - Meetings (Box 420, Folder 2)
    - Greenrock - Pocantico Hills - Memos (Box 420, Folder 3)
    - Greenrock - Seal Harbor (Box 420, Folder 4)
    - Mauna Kea (Box 417, Folder 3)
    - Mauna Kea - Works of Art (Box 417, Folder 4, Box 421, Folder 1-2)
    - Pocantico Hills - A-Z (Box 421, Folder 3)
    - Pocantico Hills - Group Requests for Use of Facilities (Box 420, Folder 5)
    - Pocantico Hills - Homesites for Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 420, Folder 6)
    - Pocantico Hills - Homesites (Box 420, Folder 7)
    - Pocantico Hills - The Playhouse (Box 422, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Open in 2029.
    - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit (Box 422, Folder 2)
    - Pocantico Hills - National Trust for Historic Preservation (Box 422, Folder 3)
    - Pocantico Hills - National Trust for Historic Preservation - Rockefeller Brothers Fund (Box 422, Folder 4, Box 423, Folder 1)
    - Pocantico Hills - Planning (Box 423, Folder 2-3)
    - Pocantico Hills - Pocantico Historic Area Plans, 1986-1989 (Box 423, Folder 4)
    - Pocantico Hills - Pocantico Institute of Science and Technology in International Affairs (Proposed) (Box 424, Folder 1)
      Resticted - Open in 2042.
    - James A. Rhodes and Associates (Box 424, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller and Associates Realty (Box 424, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Group - A-Z (Box 424, Folder 4-5)
    - Rockefeller Group - Annual Review (Box 425, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Group - Mitsubishi Estate Company, Limited (Box 424, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Group - Mitsubishi Estate Company, Limited - Articles, Clippings (Box 425, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller Center - A-Z (Box 426, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller Center - Christmas Tree (Box 426, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Center - Printed Matter (Box 426, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Center - Rainbow Room (Box 427, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Center - Rivera, Diego (Box 427, Folder 2)
    - Rockresorts (Box 427, Folder 3)
    - Rockresorts - A-K (Box 427, Folder 4-5)
    - Rockresorts - L-Z (Box 428, Folder 1)
    - Rockresorts - CSX (Box 428, Folder 2)
    - Rockresorts - Carambola Beach Resort and Golf Club (Box 428, Folder 3)
    - Rockresorts - St. Barts, 1987 (Box 428, Folder 4)
    - Rockresorts - Meetings (Box 428, Folder 5)
    - Rockresorts - Caneel Bay, Inc - A-Z (Box 428, Folder 6)
    - Rockresorts - Little Dix Bay (Box 428, Folder 7)
    - Offers - A-Z (Box 429, Folder 1)
    - Stocker, Paul (Box 429, Folder 2)
    - Offers - Euro Investors Property (Box 429, Folder 3)
    - Offers - Schiubach, Henrik (Box 429, Folder 4)
  - Religion, 1987-1991; 25
    - Religion - A-E (Box 430, Folder 1-4)
    - Religion - F-L (Box 431, Folder 1-4)
    - Religion - M-R (Box 432, Folder 1-5)
    - Religion - S-Z (Box 433, Folder 1-6)
    - Religion - A-Z - Cousins (Box 443, Folder 1-13)
    - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks (Box 434, Folder 1)
    - Abraham and Friends, Inc. (Box 434, Folder 2)
    - American Friends Service Committee (Box 443, Folder 14)
    - American Jewish Congress (Box 434, Folder 3)
    - American Jewish Congress - Cousins (Box 443, Folder 15)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith (Box 434, Folder 4)
    - Appeal of Conscience Foundation (Box 435, Folder 1)
    - Archdiocese of New York (Box 435, Folder 2)
    - The Atrium (Box 435, Folder 3-4)
    - Baca (Box 436, Folder 1)
    - Center for a Post-Modern World (Box 436, Folder 2)
    - Center for Theological Inquiry (Box 436, Folder 3)
    - Choosing Our Future (Box 436, Folder 4, Box 437, Folder 1)
    - Christic Institute (Box 437, Folder 2-3, Box 438, Folder 1-3, Box 439, Folder 1-2)
    - Contemplative Visions (Box 439, Folder 3)
    - Dharma Sangha (Box 439, Folder 4)
    - Episcopal Diocese of Arkansas (Box 440, Folder 1)
    - Foundation for Co-Creation (Box 440, Folder 2)
    - Foundation for Inner Peace (Box 440, Folder 3)
    - Foundation for Shamanic Studies (Box 440, Folder 4)
    - Foundation for Shamanic Studies - Cousins (Box 443, Folder 16)
    - The Free Daist Communion (Box 440, Folder 5)
    - Friends of Creation Spirituality (Box 441, Folder 1-2)
    - Fund for the Enhancement of the Human Spirit (Box 441, Folder 3-4, Box 442, Folder 1-4)
    - Fund for the Enhancement of the Human Spirit - Meetings, 1986-1989 (Box 444, Folder 1-5, Box 445, Folder 1-4)
    - Holoform Research, Inc. (Box 446, Folder 1-4)
    - The Hospital Chaplaincy (Box 447, Folder 1-3)
    - Icorec Trust for Sacred Literature (Box 447, Folder 4)
    - Institute for Religion and Health (Box 447, Folder 5)
    - Karma Triyana Dharmachakra (Box 448, Folder 1)
    - Mailman, Joshua (Box 448, Folder 2)
    - The North American Conference on Christianity and Ecology School of Sacred Arts (Box 448, Folder 3)
    - School of Sacred Arts (Box 448, Folder 4)
    - Shomrei Adamah (Box 449, Folder 1)
    - Shomrei Adamah - Cousins (Box 443, Folder 17)
    - Spiritual Emergence Network (Box 449, Folder 2)
    - The Spiritual Life Institute (Box 449, Folder 3-4)
    - The Tibet Fund and Tibet House (Box 450, Folder 1)
    - The Tibet Fund and Tibet House - Cousins (Box 443, Folder 18)
    - The Upaya Foundation (Box 450, Folder 2)
    - Churches - A-C (Box 450, Folder 3-4)
    - Churches - D-Z (Box 451, Folder 1-3)
    - Churches - C-Z - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 443, Folder 19-23)
    - Churches - Cathedral Church of St. John the Divine (Box 452, Folder 1-3)
    - Churches - Cathedral Church of St. John the Divine - Cousins (Box 443, Folder 24)
    - Churches - Grace Cathedral, San Francisco, California (Box 452, Folder 4, Box 453, Folder 1)
    - Churches - Riverside Church (Box 453, Folder 2-3)
    - Churches - Riverside Church - Contributions (Box 453, Folder 4)
    - Churches - Riverside Church - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial Carillon (Box 453, Folder 5)
    - Churches - Riverside Church - James Lawson (Box 454, Folder 6)
    - Churches - Union Church of Pocantico Hills (Box 454, Folder 1)
    - Missions - A-Z (Box 454, Folder 2)
    - Missions - Quebec-Labrador Foundation (Box 454, Folder 3)
    - Missions - Quebec-Labrador Foundation - Cousins (Box 443, Folder 25)
    - Missions - New York City Mission Society (Box 454, Folder 4)
    - Missions - Salvation Army (Box 454, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Family, 1987-1991; 26
    - Articles (Box 455, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Family - A-Z (Box 455, Folder 2)
    - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corporation (Box 455, Folder 3)
    - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corporation - A-Z (Box 455, Folder 4)
    - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corporation - Meetings (Box 455, Folder 5)
    - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corporation - Press Release (Box 456, Folder 1)
    - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corporation - Department-Authorization Detail, Aircraft Performance Analysis and Log Report (Box 456, Folder 2-3)
    - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corporation - Finances (Box 456, Folder 4)
    - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corporation - Venrock (Box 456, Folder 5)
    - Awards (Box 456, Folder 6)
    - Awards - American Horticultural Society (Box 457, Folder 1)
    - Awards - National Building Museum (Box 457, Folder 2-3)
    - Christmas Luncheons (Box 458, Folder 1)
    - Fifth Generation (Box 458, Folder 2)
    - Trusts (Box 458, Folder 3)
    - Trusts, 1979-1981 (Box 458, Folder 4)
    - Chasin, Richard and Laura (Box 458, Folder 5)
    - Dulany, Peggy (Box 458, Folder 6)
    - Goodwin, Neva Rockefeller - A-Z (Box 458, Folder 7)
    - Goodwin, Neva Rockefeller - Copperfield Fund (Box 458, Folder 8)
    - Growald, Paul and Eileen (Box 458, Folder 9)
    - Laura R. Chasin Charitable Lead Trust (Box 460, Folder 1)
    - Mauze, Mrs. Jean-Abby R. Mauze Charitable Trust (Box 460, Folder 2-3)
    - Mauze, Mrs. Jean - Abby R. Mauze Charitable Trust - A-Z (Box 460, Folder 4)
    - Messinger, Alida Rockefeller (Box 459, Folder 1)
    - Alida Rockefeller Charitable Lead Trust (Box 459, Folder 2)
    - Alida Rockefeller Charitable Lead Trust - A-C (Box 459, Folder 3-5)
    - Alida Rockefeller Charitable Lead Trust - D-L (Box 461, Folder 1-3)
    - Alida Rockefeller Charitable Lead Trust - M-Z (Box 462, Folder 1-2)
    - Alida Rockefeller Charitable Lead Trust - Committee for National Security (Box 462, Folder 3)
    - Alida Rockefeller Charitable Lead Trust - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy (Box 462, Folder 4)
    - Alida Rockefeller Charitable Lead Trust - Northeast Midwest Institute (Box 462, Folder 5)
    - Alida Rockefeller Charitable Lead Trust - Northwest Conservation Act Coalition (Box 462, Folder 6)
    - Alida Rockefeller Charitable Lead Trust - Nuclear Control Institute (Box 463, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Alida - Giving Program (Box 463, Folder 2)
    - Morgan, Mary R. (Box 463, Folder 3)
    - O'Neill, George D. and Mrs. Abby (Box 463, Folder 4)
    - O'Neill, George D., Jr. (Box 463, Folder 5)
    - Ortiz, Carlos Alejandro and Mrs. Rachel French (Box 463, Folder 6)
    - Pierson, Joseph A. (Box 463, Folder 7)
    - Roberts, Ann R. (Box 463, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, Abby A. (Box 463, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller, David - A-B (Box 464, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, David - B-C (Box 465, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, David - C-D (Box 466, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, David - E-F (Box 467, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, David - G-H (Box 468, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, David - H-K (Box 469, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, David - K-L (Box 470, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, David - L-M (Box 471, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, David - N-P (Box 472, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, David - P-R (Box 473, Folder 1-6)
    - Rockefeller, David - S (Box 474, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, David - T-Z (Box 475, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Addresses-Remarks-Statements - A-Z (Box 476, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Addresses-Remarks-Statements - Tinker Foundation (Box 476, Folder 4, Box 477, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Articles (Box 477, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Autographs - A-Z (Box 477, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Awards - A-O (Box 477, Folder 4-6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Awards - P-Z (Box 478, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Awards - Japan (Box 478, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Beetles (Box 478, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Biography (Box 478, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David - De Larrain, Mrs. Raymondo (Margaret) (Margaret de Cuevas) (Box 478, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Birthday - (75th Birthday), 1990 (Box 478, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Dinners-Luncheons-Receptions (Box 479, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Dinners-Luncheons-Receptions - Menus, 1980-1985 (Box 479, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Dinners-Luncheons-Receptions - President Kenan Evren of Turkey (Cancelled) (Box 479, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - 50th Wedding Anniversary (Box 479, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Frisby, Owen (Box 479, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Gifts (Box 479, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Interviews - A-Z (Box 480, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Interviews - The Yomiuri Shimbun (Box 480, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Investments - A-Z (Box 480, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Invitations to Speak - A-L (Box 480, Folder 4-5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Invitations to Speak - M-Z (Box 481, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Levingston, Bruce (Box 481, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Mailing List (Box 486, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Office (Box 481, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Peterson, Peter G. (Box 481, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Photos - A-Z (Box 482, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Radio/TV (Box 482, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Property (Box 482, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Property - Seal Harbor (Box 482, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Property - Seal Harbor - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden (Box 482, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Reed, Jospeh, V., Jr. (Box 483, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Roberts, Ann R. (Box 486, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trips - A-Z (Box 483, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trips - Europe, 1990 June (Box 483, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trips - Europe, 1988 March (Box 483, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trips - Europe, 1987 October (Box 483, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trips - Europe, 1987 March (Box 483, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trips - Latin America, 1991 (Box 483, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trips - Latin America, 1988 (Box 483, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trips - Latin America, 1987 February (Box 483, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trips - Middle East, 1990 February (Box 483, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trusts (Box 486, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Umbricht, Dr. Victor H. (Box 484, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Works of Art - A-Z (Box 485, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Works of Art - Porcelains (Box 485, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs. David (Margaret McGrath, "Peggy") - A-Z (Box 485, Folder 4-5)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs. David (Margaret McGrath, "Peggy") (Box 486, Folder 4)
      Restricted - Confidential material.
    - Rockefeller, David, Jr. - A-Z (Box 486, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Ingrid R. (Box 486, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Jennifer (Box 486, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, John D. - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary of JDR Senior's Birth - Conference and Celebration, 1989 October 26-28 (Box 485, Folder 6, Box 487, Folder 1-3, Box 488)
    - Rockefeller, John D. - A-Z (Box 488, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, John D. - Lake View Cemetery Foundation (Box 489, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, John D. - John D. Rockefeller Family Cemetery Corporation (Box 486, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, John D. - Trusts - De Cuevas Trust, 1979-1990 (Box 486, Folder 9, Box 491, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. (Box 489, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Awards (Box 489, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs. John D., Jr. (Abby Aldrich) (Box 489, Folder 4)